("HERE WITHOUT YOU"
BY 3 DOORS DOWN)
♪ A HUNDRED DAYS
HAVE MADE ME OLDER ♪
♪ SINCE THE LAST TIME THAT
I SAW YOUR PRETTY FACE ♪
♪ A THOUSAND LIES
HAVE MADE ME COLDER ♪
♪ AND I DON'T THINK I CAN
LOOK AT THIS THE SAME ♪
♪ BUT ALL THE MILES
THAT SEPARATE ♪
♪ DISAPPEAR NOW WHEN I'M
DREAMING OF YOUR FACE ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
ON MY LONELY MIND ♪
♪ I THINK ABOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ AND I DREAM ABOUT
YOU ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
WITH ME IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ AND TONIGHT IT'S
ONLY YOU AND ME ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ THE MILES JUST KEEP ROLLIN' ♪
♪ AS THE PEOPLE LEAVE
THEIR WAY TO SAY HELLO ♪
♪ I'VE HEARD THIS
LIFE IS OVERRATED ♪
♪ BUT I HOPE THAT IT
GETS BETTER AS WE GO ♪
♪ OH YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
ON MY LONELY MIND ♪
♪ I THINK ABOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ AND I DREAM ABOUT
YOU ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
WITH ME IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ AND TONIGHT, GIRL,
IT'S ONLY YOU AND ME ♪
♪ EVERYTHING I KNOW ♪
♪ AND ANYWHERE I GO ♪
♪ IT GETS HARD ♪
♪ BUT IT WON'T
TAKE AWAY MY LOVE ♪
♪ AND WHEN THE LAST ONE FALLS ♪
♪ WHEN IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE ♪
♪ IT GETS HARD ♪
♪ BUT IT WON'T
TAKE AWAY MY LOVE ♪
♪ WOAH ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
ON MY LONELY MIND ♪
♪ I THINK ABOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ AND I DREAM ABOUT
YOU ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ I'M HERE WITHOUT YOU, BABY ♪
♪ BUT YOU'RE STILL
WITH ME IN MY DREAMS ♪
♪ AND TONIGHT, GIRL,
IT'S ONLY YOU AND ME ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ OH ♪